accountwarehouse.com 2019-04-22

# Buy Game Accounts, Sell Game Accounts | Account Warehouse

**AccountWarehouse.com Privacy Policy**

The AccountWarehouse.com website and all other related services are products of AccountWarehouse.com, LLC, a Texas limited liability company (“AccountWarehouse.com,” “we,” or “us”). We take your privacy very seriously. How we will handle information we learn about you depends upon what you do when using the website located at [www.AccountWarehouse.com](http://www.accountwarehouse.com/) (“Site”). We strive to make all choices you (“you,” “User,” or “Users”) make while using our Site as transparent as possible. We also hold the security of your personal information as our top priority. This policy will cover personally identifiable information and other information that may or may not be anonymous that you provide us through use of the Site (“Privacy Policy”). All other information given to us is outside the scope of this policy. This policy will explain what information is collected, how that information is used and/or shared, how the information is protected, and how you can control your privacy while using the service. We reserve the right to make changes to this policy at any time and will update these terms on our website when we do so. 

**_Information AccountWarehouse.com Collects_**

In administering the Site, we may collect your Personal Information and non-Personal Information. Personal Information is information, that by its very nature, can be tracked back to you (“Personal Information”). Some example of this type of information includes your name, address, email address, and billing information. Non-Personal Information, on the other hand, is information that is considered insufficient to be able linked back to the original User. ****

_Personal Information Provided to AccountWarehouse.com by Users_

On the Site, all transactions are performed as if you are a guest and you do not need to create an account. To facilitate these transactions, however, you will be required to enter certain Personal Information including, but not limited to, your name, email address, address, billing information, game profile username, and game profile password. You may also screenshots, notes, and other similar information during regular use of the Site. 

**_Information Automatically Collected by AccountWarehouse.com_ **

Like other websites or apps, we also may collect and store information that is generated automatically as you navigate through our Site. We may collect information about your visit from the browser on your computer or mobile device including but not limited to the time and date you access the Site, IP address, cookies, and the pages you request — to analyze trends, administer the Site, track navigation of the site, deliver relevant advertisements and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use (note that IP addresses are not linked to Personal Information). We use this information to improve understanding of customer needs and provide relevant services. To automatically collect information, we use various technologies including: 

Cookies. Cookies are small data files that a website you visit may save on your hard drive that usually includes an anonymous unique identifier. The cookie does not personally identify the user; it merely identiﬁes the computer with which the user accesses the Site. Unless a user voluntarily identiﬁes himself or herself (through registration, for example), the Site will not be able to ascertain the identity of the user, even if a cookie is assigned to a user’s computer. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information supplied by a user. A cookie cannot retrieve any other data from your hard drive, pass on computer viruses, or capture your e-mail address. The Site uses cookies for user authentication, keeping track of your preferences, promotional campaigns that require user identification, keeping track of our audience size and traffic patterns, and in certain other cases. You can configure your browser to accept cookies, reject cookies or notify you when a cookie is being used; however, if you do so it may render your computer unable to take advantage of the personalized features enjoyed by other users of the Site. Cookies allow us to provide better security on the Site, to customize the content, to track purchases, and to keep the Site working properly. 

Pixel Tags. We use "Pixel Tags" (also referred to as clear Gifs, Web beacons or Web bugs). Pixel tags are tiny graphic images with a unique identifier, similar in function to Cookies, that are used to track online movements of web users. In contrast to Cookies, which are stored on a computer’s hard drive or web browser, Pixel Tags are embedded invisibly in web pages. Pixel Tags also allow us to send email messages in a format that users can read, and tell us whether emails have been opened to, in part, ensure that we are sending only messages that are of interest to our users. We may also use this information to reduce or eliminate messages sent to a user. 

Log File Information. When you use AccountWarehouse.com, our servers may automatically record certain information that your device sends whenever you visit any website and use certain apps. These server logs may include information such as your web or app request, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser language, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time of your request, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. 

Threat Detection. We use certain third party service providers to provide threat detection, user authentication and fraud prevention services. These service providers may automatically collect certain information about your visits to the Site and the device you use to connect to our Site, in order to monitor for potential threats or bad actors. This information may include, among other things, your IP address and your device’s unique device identifier. 

Information Collected from Other Sources. We may supplement the information we have about you with information received from other sources including from our pages on social networking sites, the social networking sites themselves, and from commercially available sources (e.g., data brokers and public databases). The information we receive may include demographic data such as age, gender and income level, your interests and purchase data and other information that is necessary or useful to assist our marketing efforts or for user verification, authentication, fraud detection or to comply with regulatory requirements. 

Third Party Analytics. We use a number of third party service providers, such as Google Analytics, to help analyze how users use our services (" **Analytics Companies** "). These Analytics Companies use Cookies to collect information such as how often users visit our Site, what pages they visit, and what other sites they used prior to coming to our Site. We use the information we get from Analytics Companies only to improve our Site. 

**_How We Use Your Data_**

We will use the information you provide to us for a variety of purposes, including to: 

  * contact you regarding a transaction; 
  * contact you for customer service requests; 
  * contact you regarding payment issues; 
  * operate, improve and maintain our products and services, including analyzing user behavior; 
  * administer promotions, provide features and display relevant content to you; 
  * track and monitor web traﬃc; 
  * interact with support and feedback platforms; 
  * manage support and contact requests; 
  * tailor and optimize advertising, and 
  * to implement SPAM protection. 

**_How We May Share Your Information_**

We don’t give your Personal Information to any third-party services, except when it’s necessary to provide services (like when we partner with payment processors or other data services). When we share data with third-party services that support our delivery of the Site, we require that they protect your Personal Information to the same standards we do. We do reserve the right to disclose Personal Information when we believe that doing so is reasonably necessary to comply with the law or law enforcement, to prevent fraud or abuse, or to protect our legal rights. 

Please see below for how we may share your Personal and non-Personal Information. 

**_Sharing of Personal Information_**

When you send information through the Site, you are granting us permission to use and take other actions regarding such information, to provide the Site. We do not share, sell, rent or otherwise distribute this information to others, except as disclosed in this Privacy Policy. We may share your information with third parties outside of AccountWarehouse.com under the following circumstances: 

  1. _With Your Consent_ : We may share information when you provide us with your consent to do so. This may occur when you consent aﬃrmatively or it may occur through your use of the Site as provided in this Privacy Policy. 
  2. _Service Providers and Contractors_ : We reserve the right to disclose to service providers, contractors, or other third parties any or all of the information that we collect online about you and other visitors to conduct business on our behalf. These activities could include processing payments, maintaining the Site, or facilitating email delivery to you. We require that our service providers protect your Personal Information with the same standards we do but we are not responsible for their policies or practices. 
  3. _By Law or to Protect Rights_ : We may disclose information when we believe that disclosure is necessary to comply with the law, to enforce our intellectual property rights, to enforce our Terms of Service, or to protect the rights, property or safety of AccountWarehouse.com and our employees, and if necessary to defend against third-party claims. This specifically includes credit bureaus with which we may report information about late payments, missed payments, or other defaults on your account. We may also disclose information when requested to comply with a court order, investigation, or governmental request. 
  4. _Business Transfers_ : If we go through a business transfer, such as consolidation, merger, restructuring, acquisition, or sale of part or all of our assets, you acknowledge and consent to the transfer of your information. You further acknowledge and consent to the continued use of your information by the recipient so long as they comply with this Privacy Policy. 
  5. _Tax Filings_. If your earnings from a sale of an account exceeds a certain threshold, in accordance with our interpretation of applicable law, we will disclose the amount of your earnings and other related information to the United States Internal Revenue Service and other appropriate taxing authorities. 

Please bear in mind that whenever you voluntarily make your Personal Information available for viewing by third parties online – for example through comments and participation in forums or through email – that information can be seen, collected and used by others besides us. We cannot be responsible for any unauthorized third-party use of such information. 

**_Sharing of Non-Personal Information and Aggregate Data_ **

AccountWarehouse.com may share with third parties your non-Personal Information and related aggregated data for any legitimate business purposes, including for reporting, research, or advertising. Because this form of data does not identify particular users, these third parties will not be able to contact you based solely on this data. For example, we may share aggregated usage data from our Users or may share IP addresses or general demographic information of our users to provide anonymous aggregated data to business partners about the volume of use on the Site and the opportunities in which Users are most interested. 

**_How We Protect All of Our Data_**

All information submitted to AccountWarehouse.com will be stored on our servers. We will use industry standard measures, including encryption where appropriate. However, as eﬀective as the reasonable security measures we implement may be, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information supplied will not be intercepted while being transmitted over the Internet. Therefore, any information you transmit to us is sent at your own risk. 

By using the Site or providing Personal Information to us, you agree that we may communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy, and administrative issues relating to your use of the Site. If we learn of a security system’s breach, we may attempt to notify you electronically by posting a notice on the Site or sending an email to you. 

**_How You Can Control the Information We Collect, Use and Share_ **

You can stop using the Site at anytime. If you would like to stop receiving emails from us please select the “unsubscribe” link located at the bottom of the emails you may receive from us. 

On request, we will give you a copy of all the Personal Information about you that we hold. This information is subject to a fee not exceeding the prescribed fee permitted by law. 

We may retain certain information as required by law or for necessary business purposes. We are under no obligation to store such Personal Information indefinitely and disclaim any liability arising out of, or related to, the destruction of such Personal Information. In addition, you should be aware that it is not always possible to completely remove or delete all of your information from our databases without some residual data because of backups and other reasons. We are under no obligation to destroy anonymized aggregate data. 

Regardless of your choices regarding promotional communications and updates regarding content we may send you administrative messages regarding transactions or other similar communications, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them. 

**_Links_**

The Site may contain links to other sites or services. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or other practices employed by websites linked to, or from, our website nor the information or content contained therein. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by our Site. 

**_Our Policy Toward Children_** __

The Site is not directed to children under the age of 13. We will not knowingly maintain personally identiﬁable information from or about anyone under 13. If we become aware that we have collected personally identiﬁable information from a user of the Site that is under the age of 13, then we will remove that child’s Personal Information from our ﬁles. If a parent or guardian learns his or her child has provided us with Personal Information, he or she should contact us at [admin@AccountWarehouse.com ](mailto:admin@AccountWarehouse.com) (please include the child’s name, address, and e-mail address). 

**_Consent to Transfer_**

Our computer systems for the Site are currently governed by and operated in the United States, so your personal data will be processed by us in the United States, where data protection and privacy regulations may not offer the same level of protection as in other parts of the world, such as the European Union. AccountWarehouse.com makes no representation that the Site is governed by or operated in accordance with the laws of any other nation. If you are a visitor from outside the United States, by using the Site, you agree to this Privacy Policy and you consent to the transfer of all such information to the United States, which may not offer an equivalent level of protection of that required in the European Union or other countries, and to the processing of that information as described in this Policy. 

**_Changes and Updates_**

From time to time, we may change this Privacy Policy. To ensure that you are familiar with our most updated policies and practices, you should check the effective date indicated at the end of this Privacy Policy each time you use the Site. You will be bound by any such changes to the policy when you use the Site after those changes have been posted. If we make material revisions concern practices where we have represented we will obtain your consent to use or disclose your Personal Information, we will obtain your consent before taking any action inconsistent with those representations. 

**_Contact Us_**

We welcome your feedback regarding this Privacy Policy. If you have questions, comments, or concerns about either one, please contact us by e-mail at [sales@AccountWarehouse.com](mailto:sales@AccountWarehouse.com). 

End. 

May 22, 2017
